<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Hugo Apéro</title>
    <link>/pubs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Hugo Apéro</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/pubs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distancing Regulates the Effect of Incidental Anger (vs. Fear) on Affective Decision-Making Under Uncertainty</title>
      <link>/pubs/jbdm2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/jbdm2024/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Emotions integral to a task are often adaptive, particularly in situations where outcomes and probabilities are not known. However, decisions are also influenced by emotions that arise from situations unrelated to the task. This is especially the case with negative emotions like fear and anger, which also tend to be accompanied by ruminative thinking that might divert decision-makers&amp;rsquo; attention from the task at hand. In two preregistered experiments, we show how self-distancing regulates the influence of incidental anger (vs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Versus Bright Side of a Smiley: A Preregistered Replication of Experiment 3 in Glikson et al. (2018)</title>
      <link>/pubs/smiley/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/smiley/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The present paper reports an independent and better powered replication of Experiment 3 in Glikson et al. (2018). The authors of the original study reported support for their proposition that due to perceptions of (in)appropriateness, the use of smileys may backfire and produce less favorable perceptions of competence in a formal work-related setting, yet more favorable perceptions of warmth in an informal work-related setting. Our results, in contrast, indicated that smileys produce a negative effect on perceptions of competence and a positive effect on perceptions of warmth, regardless of the level of formality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual Differences in Fear and Self-Distancing Predict Information Processing via Problem Construal</title>
      <link>/pubs/paid2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/paid2023/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial Advisors Rely Less on Intuition and Are More Risk-Averse When Deciding for Their Clients</title>
      <link>/pubs/selfclient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/selfclient/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting representativeness classic paradigms: Replication and extensions of the problems reviewed in Kahneman and Tversky (1972)</title>
      <link>/pubs/repheuristic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/repheuristic/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-office noise and information processing</title>
      <link>/pubs/jmp2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/jmp2023/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and anxiety differ in construal level and scope</title>
      <link>/pubs/ce2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/ce2023/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The fear-anxiety distinction has been extensively discussed and debated among emotion researchers. In this study, we tested this distinction from a social-cognitive perspective. Drawing on construal level theory and regulatory scope theory, we examined whether fear and anxiety differ in their underlying level of construal and scope. Results from a preregistered autobiographical recall study (N = 200) that concerned either a fear situation or an anxiety situation and a large dataset from Twitter (N = 104,949) indicated that anxiety was associated with a higher level of construal and a more expansive scope than fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speakers’ Choice of Frame Reveals Little about Their Trait Emotions but More about Their Preferences and Risk Perception</title>
      <link>/pubs/framing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/framing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distancing Moderates the Effect of Incidental Fear vs. Anger on Risk Taking and Loss Aversion</title>
      <link>/pubs/aom2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/aom2022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National identity predicts public health support during a global pandemic</title>
      <link>/pubs/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/covid/</guid>
      <description>Changing collective behaviour and supporting non-pharmaceutical interventions is an important component in mitigating virus transmission during a pandemic. In a large international collaboration (Study 1, N = 49,968 across 67 countries), we investigated selfreported factors associated with public health behaviours (e.g., spatial distancing and stricter hygiene) and endorsed public policy interventions (e.g., closing bars and restaurants) during the early stage of the COVID-19 pandemic (April-May 2020). Respondents who reported identifying more strongly with their nation consistently reported greater engagement in public health behaviours and support for public health policies. Results were similar for representative and non-representative national samples. Study 2 (N = 42 countries) conceptually replicated the central finding using aggregate indices of national identity (obtained using the World Values Survey) and a measure of actual behaviour change during the pandemic (obtained from Google mobility reports). Higher levels of national identification prior to the pandemic predicted lower mobility during the early stage of the pandemic (r = −0.40). We discuss the potential implications of links between national identity, leadership, and public health for managing COVID-19 and future pandemics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arousal and Risk Taking: The Moderating Role of Reappraisal</title>
      <link>/pubs/aom2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/aom2021/</guid>
      <description>Researchers have provided important insight into the cognitive and emotional aspects of risk taking. In the present study we investigated how incidental physiological arousal — an affective component that has received relatively little attention — influences risk taking and cognitive processing. Moreover, to gain further insight into the relation between arousal and risky decision making, we examined the moderating role of the reappraisal strategy of emotion regulation. We found that incidental physiological arousal and intuitive processing predicted a higher likelihood of risk taking, whereas analytical processing predicted a lower likelihood of risk taking. Furthermore, we found that the relationship between physiological arousal and risk taking was stronger among individuals low on habitual cognitive reappraisal. Overall, the present study contributes to dual process theories of decision making and a growing line of research on emotion regulation and risk taking. Implications and directions for future research are discussed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear from Afar, Not So Risky After All. Distancing Moderates the Relationship Between Fear and Risk Taking</title>
      <link>/pubs/fearfromafar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/fearfromafar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Replication of Study 1 in Differentiating Social and Personal Power by Lammers, Stoker, and Stapel (2009)</title>
      <link>/pubs/sp2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/pubs/sp2019/</guid>
      <description>Abstract We performed an independent, direct, and better powered (N = 295) replication of Study 1, an experiment (N = 113) by Lammers, Stoker, and Stapel (2009). Lammers and colleagues distinguished between social power (influence over others) and personal power (freedom from the influence of others), and found support for their predictions that the two forms of power produce opposite effects on stereotyping, but parallel effects on behavioral approach. Our results did not replicate the effects on behavioral approach, but partially replicated the effects on stereotyping.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
